Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) PE.021
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: State, Regional, and Central Council Files, 1956-2007; 2.25 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 shared oversize box
  - New Jersey State Industrial Union Council, 1977-2000 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1966-2005, undated (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Affiliated Organizations, Roster of, 1974 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Circular Letters, 1964-1997 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Constitutions, 1962-1969, undated (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Constitutions, 1971-1996 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Conventions, 1970-2000 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Fliers, 1992-2007, undated (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: History, 1988-1990 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Labor Recognition Dinners, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Labor Recognition Dinners, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Labor Recognition Dinners, 1999 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Labor Recognition Dinners, 2000 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Legislature, Publications Relating to, 1959-2001, undated (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Newsletters and Memorandum, 1985-1995, undated (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Pamphlets and Publications, 1980-1993, undated (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Pamphlets and Publications, 1997-2000 (Box 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO: Press Releases, 1960-1978 (Box 11)
  - Ohio AFL-CIO, 1960-1984 (Box 11)
  - Rhode Island AFL-CIO, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Rochester Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1994, 1997 (Box 11)
  - San Francisco Labor Council, circa 1960 (Box 11)
  - St. Louis Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Tennessee State Labor Council, 1961, undated (Box 11)
  - Texas AFL-CIO, 1957-1959, 1989-1997, undated (Box 11)
  - Washington Central Labor Union, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Westchester County AFL-CIO Central Labor Body, 1959 (Box 11)
  - Wisconsin AFL-CIO, circa 1997 (Box 11)
- Series III: New York City Central Labor Council Files, 1959-2005; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 shared manuscript box
  - AFSCME District Council 37, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Alerts, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
  - Alerts, 1989-1999 (Box 12)
  - Automation/Shorter Work Week, 1960, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Black Trade Unionist Leadership Committee, 1974-1984, 1996, undated (Box 12)
  - Central Labor Rehabilitation Council (I), 1967-1995 (Box 12)
  - Central Labor Rehabilitation Council (II), 1967-1995 (Box 12)
  - Circular Letters, 1981-1998, undated (Box 12)
  - Civil Rights Committee, 1960, undated (Box 12)
  - Civil Rights Conference, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Committees, undated (Box 12)
  - Community Services Committee, 1969-1989, undated (Box 12)
  - Constitution/By-Laws, 1987-1988, undated (Box 12)
  - Delegate Entitlement/Voting: Affiliates, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Dance Program, 1980-1995 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Dance Program, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Dance Program, 1998-1999 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Dance Program, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Dance Program, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Education Committee, 1965, 1967, undated (Box 12)
  - Fliers and Ephemera, 1981-2005, undated (Box 12)
  - Hispanic Labor Committee, 1977-1996 (Box 12)
  - Hospital and Medical Care Committee, 1961 (Box 12)
  - Labor Day Parade, 1981-1993, undated (Box 12)
  - Lawyers Committee, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Legislative: Labor Candidates, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Local Unions, 1964, undated (Box 12)
  - Memoranda, 1984-1997 (Box 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings/Articles, 1987-1992, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Pamphlets and Publications, 1959-1960, 1988, undated (Box 12)
  - Project Rehab, 1966-1968 (Box 12)
  - September 11 Memorial Service, April 26, 2002 (Box Shared Tamiment 062, Folder 26)
  - Trade Union Handbook, 1977-1997 (Box 12)
  - Trade Union Leadership Institute, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Utility Workers Union of America: Local 1-2, 1991 (Box 12)